Aah!
Aah! Uh!
Uhh!
Holy oil!
Okay. move!
Oh!
Pfft.
Whoa.
Is it over?
Yeah. Yes.
Uh. sorry about the mess.
You boys just took down
an evil plushie
that was trying to kill me.
We're all good.
Alan?
Everything okay in here?
- Oh. uh. hey. Jay.
- I heard the ruckus next door. and I...
What in the...What...
holy heck?
It -- it was a-a...
- Did they do this?
- No. Naw. it was a...
Defective product.
Yeah. sometimes the batteries
in these...
giant stuffed dinosaurs
just explode.
Yeah. never buy anything
from Mooselyvania.
Mm.
Exactly. Mm.
- Okay.
- Uh. guys. this is Jay.
He's the big man around
this neighborhood.
Owns practically
the whole damn thing --
the Chinese joint.
the laundromat.
Great. Great. great. great.
Yeah. that's very cool.
Can you guys give us a second?
- Great.
- Nice cover.
What the hell was that?
I mean. we rolled into town
because people were seeing
a lizard monster.
And yes.
we tracked it back here.
but no way did I think we'd end up --
- Killing Barney?
Yeah.
Was pretty satisfying.
though. wasn't it?
Probably just
a cursed object.
Well. it didn't act like
We should probably do
some digging.
Everything all right?
Yeah. Yeah. great.
Yeah. Uh. we were
just gonna head out.
Oh. hold up.
You boys saved my life.
Anything you want. it's yours.
We could never. We're --
we're just happy we could help.
Wait. Uh...
anything?
Hmm.
Dean. this is ridiculous.
Look. giving us this
made him feel good. okay?
- Yeah. where are you gonna put this? You...
- I'm the good guy.
Hey. whoa. whoa. whoa.
whoa. whoa! Take it easy!
What?
She's delicate!
She...Pfft.
Go that way. I'll lead.
W-what?
Yeah. Dean...
Shh.
Dude. watch out.
Hey. what are you doin'?
Uh. research.
Okay.
You know.
it's the strangest thing.
I-I can't find anything
on a-a cursed object
that actually
physically attacks people.
Dude. it's over. All right?
Be like Elsa -- Let it go.
"Be like Elsa"?
Ah? Right?
Come here. I need to show you
something. It's important.
Come on.
Behold...
the Dean-cave.
Or Fortress of Dean-a-tude.
Just -- still trying
to figure that one out.
We got Foosball.
We've got jukebox --
all vinyl. obviously.
Double La-Z-Boy recliners.
And. of course. the bar.
Still a work-in-progress.
It's gonna have a kegerator
because...Well. it's gonna.
And finally...
the pièce de résistance.
Okay. hold on. hold on.
When did you have time
to do all this?
When it's important.
you make time. Sammy.
Wh--
Let's give this bad boy
a test run. huh?
♪ Dun. dun ♪
♪ Dun... ♪
♪ Dun. Na! ♪
What the hell?
Dean? What just...
Aah!
You're a cartoon!
I'm a cartoon!
Uh. is -- is this...
Okay. okay. okay.
This is dream.
It's gotta be a --
Dude!
It's not a dream.
Holy crap.
This is. uh...
You saw that light.
D-did we just get sucked
into the TV?
Or maybe this
is an angel thing.
Or -- or the Trickster.
No. he's dead.
Or is he?
Dean. what the hell?
I don't know. Sam. I...
Whoa.
Uh...
How did the car get here?
I had the keys in my pocket?
Or maybe -- Wait. seriously?
That's what's bumping you
about this?
Okay. look. are we animated?
Yes.
Is it weird? Yes.
It's beyond weird.
Well. and "beyond weird"
is kind of our thing.
So whatever happened.
we'll figure it out.
This is a case.
so let's work it.
How?
Same as always.
We drive.
A malt shop. Really?
Look. let's just head in.
ask around.
see what we can see.
Oh. my God.
That -- that -- that --
that's. uh. that's...
That's the Mystery Machine.
We're not just in any cartoon.
We're in Scooby-Doo!
♪ Supernatural 13x16 ♪
Scoobynatural
Original Air Date on March 29. 2018
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man
Oh!
That's
the freakin' Scooby Gang!
Here you are.
Four milkshakes.
Great. So we're stuck in
a cartoon with a talking dog.
Not just any talking dog.
the talking dog.
The greatest talking dog
in history.
Now come on!
Dibs on Daphne.
Jeepers!
Those sure were
some super groovy tunes.
Oh. man. This is like a dream come true.
Your dream is to hang out
with the Scooby Gang?
Sam. growing up on the road.
no matter where Dad dragged us.
no matter what we did.
there was always a TV.
And you know what
was always on that TV?
Scooby and the gang.
These guys. they're our
friggin' role models. man.
Except Fred. He's a wad.
He's...What?
Just think about it --
we do the same thing.
We go to spooky places.
we solve mysteries.
we fight ghosts.
Yeah. except our ghosts
don't wear masks.
and we don't have
a talking dog.
I don't know. I mean. Cass is
kind of like a talking dog.
Now. how do I look?
-Two-dimensional.
-Perfect!
Uh...hi.
Huh?
Uh. uh. I'm Dean. My brother. Sam.
Mind if we join you?
Of course not!
There's plenty of room.
I'm Fred.
This is Velma. Shaggy.
Scooby. and --
Daphne.
Hmm?
Enchanté.
Hmm.
Of course we know you.
You guys are famous.
Famous?
Like. the only thing we're
famous for is our eating skills.
Yum. yum. yum.
So looks like you guys
are celebrating something?
We are!
We just found out
that Scooby's been named as one
of the heirs to a fortune.
left to him by an old Southern colonel.
Scooby saved him from drowning
in a fish pond.
I'm a hero.
Scooby.
Okay. okay.
But he's dead now. right?
Uh. yeah.
Uh. cancer.
Give us a second.
Hey. you wanna
pull that stick out of your...
nether regions
and just play along here?
Play...
There are no words in this newspaper. Dean.
We should be trying
to get out of here
and instead. you -- you're
hanging out with Marmaduke.
How dare you!
And hitting on Daphne.
when she's clearly with Fred.
She's settling. all right?
Oh. Daphne could do
so much better.
Last time we got zapped into TV.
we got out by playing our part.
This is probably like that.
The gang. they're about
to get a mystery.
I don't know. gang.
Sounds like this could be
the start of a mystery.
You know. uh. Sam and I
are actually
mystery solvers. too.
Mind if we tag along?
That sounds like a swell idea.
In fact. I think it's high time
we hit the road.
You know what that means?
Uh-huh!
Road food!
Oh. heck. yes!
Sam! Sam!
Look how big my mouth is!
Hey. why don't you guys follow
us up to the Colonel's mansion?
I don't know. Freddie. I'm not
sure Baby can go that slow.
Well. the Mystery Machine is
a lot faster than it looks.
Oh. yeah? Well. let's see
who can get there first.
Or are you...chicken?
Well. I'm game if you are.
Hey. why do you hate Fred
so much?
He thinks he's so cool.
with his perfect hair.
his can-do attitude.
that stupid ascot.
Let's do this!
Did... did you
just get beat by a microvan?
The light was red!
The light...
Fred!
Look. all I'm saying is that.
aerodynamically speaking.
there is no way my Baby
should lose to...
that. Unless Fred cheated.
which he clearly did.
Dude. get over it.
No!
"A Night of Fright
is No Delight."
What?
That's the episode we're in.
I've seen it. like.
a million times.
Attention. everybody.
As you all know.
I am Cosgood Creeps.
attorney of
the late Colonel Sanders.
Shut up.
My client was a bit odd.
His only directions were
to play this record for you.
Yeah! Classic vinyl.
Greetin's. y'all!
Cousin Simple. Nephew Norble.
Sweet Cousin Maldahyde.
Cousin Slicker.
and my old friend. Scooby-Doo.
You're all gonna receive
an equal share of $1 million.
providing you spend tonight
here in the old family mansion.
Oh. one more thing --
the house is haunted.
Haunted?
Yes. haunted.
And if any of you can't
make it through the night.
his or her share of my fortune
will go to the others.
Now good night
and pleasant dreams. y'all.
Oh. boy.
What kind of a weirdo
sets all this up?
I mean. spend the night in
a haunted house for $1 million?
That can't be legal.
Sam. come on. The house
isn't really haunted.
- I'm not --
- And things like this happen all the time.
Oh. yeah.
maybe in a car--
Dude. what's wrong
with you?
They don't know that
they're in a...a C-word.
And we're not gonna
tell 'em about anything.
Not where we're from.
not about monsters.
Nothing. Capiche?
They are pure
and innocent and good.
and we're gonna
keep it that way.
Look.
if you've seen this episode.
why -- why can't we just
skip to the end?
Well. 'cause sometimes
it's about the journey
and not the destination.
Or do you just want more time
to try and get with Daphne?
Do not ruin this for me!
I'll return
to the house in the morning
to find out which of you remain.
if any.
Turns out.
he's the bad guy.
You don't say.
10:00.
and I suggest we all
turn in.
So. Daphne...
old drafty house.
What say you and I bunk together?
Oh. Dean! Boys and girls don't
sleep in the same room. silly.
Come on. Velma.
Guess you're with me.
slugger.
Awesome.
Relax. Scooby. We'll spend
the night with ya.
Now let's hit the sack.
Are you wearing...
a nightgown?
It's called a sleeping robe.
Between you and me.
it's freakin' comfortable.
It's like
I'm wrapped in hugs.
So those new guys are
kinda groovy.
Sure. Dean's all right.
But that big lug...
What a dummy.
"Haunted." Sheesh.
Like that's a real thing.
Huh.
What?
Oh. nothing. Just...
I thought big lugs were
kinda your thing.
Huh? Pssh.
Hmm?
Huh?
Mm.
Is that all you're gonna do? Eat?
Relax. In a few minutes.
we're gonna find out that
Cousin Simple's missing.
the Scoobies are gonna think
that it's a ghost.
but really. it's just the lawyer
Cosgood Creeps in disguise.
Told ya.
Come on. gang!
Let's check it out!
Oh. no!
Wait. wait. wait.
No. the dummy bodies don't
show up until later.
Dean. this isn't a dummy.
This is blood.
He's -- he's dead.
Like -- like. really.
actually dead.
Jinkies!
Jeepers!
Zoinks!
Ruh-roh!
Son of a bitch.
Well. gang. it looks like
we've got another mystery
on our hands.
Are you kidding me. Fred?
Dude. someone's dead.
A little respect.
Yeah. Fred.
He can be such a jerk.
- Right. Daphne?
- Not really.
We should look for evidence...
Huh?!
like fingerprints or fluids.
Uh-huh!
Fluids?
Dude. this is not
the way things went down
in the episode.
I remember everything
that happened in Scooby-Doo.
and no one ever got
stabbed in the back
and ended up in a pool
of their own blood.
Yeah. Yeah. okay.
Um. so. if that guy can die
for real in this cartoon.
that means we can. too.
It doesn't matter if we die.
Scooby-Doo could die!
And that's not happening.
not on my watch.
I'd take a bullet for that dog.
There has to be a logical
explanation for what's going on.
Besides a ghost hunting
us down to collect an inheritance?
Yeah. what he said.
What would a ghost need with money?
Precisely. And besides.
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Huh?
So once you eliminate
the impossible.
whatever remains.
no matter how improbable.
must be the truth.
Look!
-Uhh!
-Gotcha!
Uhh! Aah! Uhh!
Not today. freak!
Cass?
Like. you know this guy?
Uh. yeah. yeah. He's a --
he's a friend of ours.
Neato!
Castiel. the Scooby Gang.
Castiel? It sounds like
a great Italian pizza place.
Uh. it's a pleasure to meet you.
Nice to meet you. too.
Sam. Dean...
this dog is talking.
- Yep.
- Cass. how did you get here?
Well. I was looking for you
at the bunker when...
Sam? Dean?
I'm back from Syria with
fruit from the Tree of Life.
The tree was guarded by
a pack of djinn.
I killed most of them.
bargained with the rest.
Think I'm...
technically married to
their queen now.
Hello?
Sam?
Hey. why don't you guys follow
us up to the Colonel's mansion?
I don't know. Freddie.
Dean?
I'm not sure Baby can
go that slow.
Well. the Mystery Machine is
a lot faster than it looks.
Oh. yeah? Well. let's see
who can get there first.
Or are you...chicken?
Well. I'm game if you are.
Hey. why do you hate Fred
so much?
He thinks he's so cool.
with his perfect hair.
his can-do attitude...
that stupid ascot.
Let's do this!
I saw purple sparks.
then a flash of light.
and the next thing I knew.
I was in this strange world.
I saw you race off...
Hey!
and I've been trying to
catch up ever since.
You saw purple sparks?
Dean. that's like with
the killer stuffed dinosaur.
And they were both in
that pawn shop.
Maybe this
is all connected.
Um. "killer stuffed dinosaur"?
Oh. I-I didn't mean a real...
It's a book we're writing.
Yeah. about...
killer stuffed dinosaurs.
It's called...
"The Killer Stuffed Dinosaur
in Love."
Huh. Great title.
Yeah. Great title.
Well. if he isn't responsible
for Cousin Simple's death.
who is?
Huh?
Like. somebody turn up
the heat in here. man.
It's getting cold.
Huh?
Yikes!
No! No! Aah!
Oh!
Sam.
Roh!
Ph-ph-ph-phantom!
Aah!
Come on. Sam. We're on.
Yah!
Uhh!
Gotcha!
Uhh! Huh?
Wait. what?
G-g-g-g-ghost!
Guys. no. It's not a ghost.
Oh. yeah? Then. man. how did he
just walk through that wall?!
Well. there's probably
a hidden door.
Well. whatever it was.
it's gone now.
It looks like he was
coming out of here.
Well. that's not good.
I think
I'm gonna be sick.
Come on. gang!
So do they always just
walk away from dead bodies or...
Sam. the cold spot.
fritzing out...
that was a ghost --
our kind of ghost.
I think this cartoon
is haunted.
All right. Prepmeister Fred.
what's your plan?
We should all split up
and search the house for clues.
That's a plan?
Mnh-mnh.
I-I don't think
we should separate.
It'll be easier for Dean and me
to keep you safe
if we're all together.
Really. Sam?
I wouldn't expect such a big.
broad-shouldered fella like you
to be as chicken as Shaggy.
No offense. Shaggy.
Like. none taken.
If this is a real ghost.
these guys are in trouble.
We can't let anything
happen to them.
Exactly. So. for now.
let's follow ascot boy's lead.
I call team up with Daphne!
Great! It'll be
just the three of us.
Sam and I will check the attic.
I mean...
unless you're too scared.
What? N-no. I-I'm...
Let's check the attic.
Like. man. I guess that
leaves me and old Scoob
with you. Castiel.
Wonderful.
I once led armies.
and now I'm paired with
a scruffy Philistine and a talking dog.
So I guess this is
your first mystery.
So if you could keep those
giant linebacker shoulders
from knocking over any clues.
that would be great.
Why do you keep talking
about my shoulders?
Oh. I. uh. huh.
Uh...
Aah!
Maybe that was the ghost.
Look. I'm not supposed
to tell you this.
but ghosts are real.
Huh?
My brother and I. we hunt them.
along with werewolves
and vampires and demons and...
We've saved the world.
A lot.
Look. Sam.
the simple fact is
monsters are nothing more
than crooks in masks --
usually unscrupulous
real estate developers.
One. there are way better
real estate scams.
- And two --
- Hey. look! A clue.
That's strange.
I guess we both noticed
that these toys are
the only things up here
that aren't covered in dust.
Actually. I was noticing this.
Ectoplasm.
This gets left behind by ghosts.
Oh. stop already.
You can't really believe
in ghosts.
Oh!
Told you.
Aah! It's not a g--
It's probably just Christmas
lights and -- and fishing line.
So. Daph.
I usually don't have
to do this.
but what do you look for
in a guy?
Oh. I don't know.
Strong. sincere.
and an ascot wouldn't hurt.
Whoa. hold on.
Check out that book.
There are a lot of books
in here. Dean.
No. that one.
The one that isn't painted into
the background of the car--
Library.
The...library.
Huh. Sorry.
I thought it might be
some kind of
secret passage or...
Aah!
Whoa!
Daphne. you okay?
Maybe I should just give you
a once-over to make sure.
Aah!
Oh! Oh. hell. no.
Like.
did someone open a window?
Yeah. it's cold in here.
Never seen a ghost
wear such a ridiculous costume.
Huh?
Aah!
Run! Run!
♪ Scooby Dooby Doo.
where are you? ♪
♪ We got some work to do now ♪
♪ Scooby Dooby Doo. where are you? ♪
Hey!
♪ We need some help
from you now ♪
♪ Come on. Scooby-Doo.
I see you ♪
♪ Pretending you got a sliver ♪
♪ You're not foolin' me
'cause I can't see ♪
♪ The way you shake and shiver ♪
Hmm.
♪ You know we got a mystery
to solve ♪
Mm-hmm.
♪ So. Scooby-Doo. be ready for your act ♪
♪ Don't hold back ♪
♪ And. Scooby-Doo. if you come through ♪
♪ You're gonna have yourself
a Scooby Snack ♪
♪ That's a fact! ♪
♪ Scooby Dooby Doo. where are you? ♪
♪ Scooby-Doo ♪
♪ You're ready and you're willin' ♪
♪ If we can count on you. Scooby-Doo ♪
♪ I know we'll catch that villain ♪
Guys!
We have to stop
this ghost.
We almost did.
Dean had him by the thigh.
He what?
I almost caught him.
That's the point.
Guys. come on.
For the last time.
there's no such thing as ghosts.
Oh. no!
That costume looks
really...real.
I'll get him.
Fred. don't!
Uhh!
Fred!
Huh?
Oh!
Uhh!
- Like. that's our cue to get out of here!
- Aah!
Run!
Aah!
Shaggy!
Dean! Iron!
- Oh!
Ah!
What just happened?
Where's Shaggy?
Over here!
Like. little help?
- [ Shaggy screaming in
- Shaggy!
Scooby!
Gotcha!
You've got me!
Who's got you?!
Oh!
Aah!
Shaggy!
Shaggy! Are you okay?
Like. do I look like
I'm okay?
It appears his arm is broken.
What? That's not --
I have jumped out of a biplane
in a museum and was fine!
How did this happen?!
I-I don't know. I...
Something threw me
across the room.
Wires. Probably just wires.
Like. hello!
Broken arm here!
Shaggy. brace yourself.
Uhh!
Fred.
give me your ascot.
Dean. we have to tell them
the truth.
What truth?
The truth about the phantom.
Look. this phantom isn't like
other ghosts you've faced.
He's real. He is a real ghost.
Huh?
Um. I'm not totally
following you.
Look. that isn't a guy
in a mask and a costume.
It's a vengeful spirit that's
come back from the dead.
That's the truth.
So everything you told me.
it's true?
Mm-hmm.
Werewolves? Vampires?
Demons?
Mm-hmm.
I thought I was blind
without my glasses.
but I was just blind.
Oh. how could I be
so stupid?
Uh. well. I mean...
We've been stopping
real estate developers
when we could've been
hunting Dracula?
Are you kidding me?!
- Ooh. Ah. - Uh...
- My life is meaningless!
If there are ghosts...
that means there's an afterlife.
Heaven. Hell.
Am I going to hell?!
We told you
every freaking time!
But did you ever listen
to Scoob and me? No!
- We're doomed.
- All right. knock it off!
Come on! Scooby Gang does not
have nervous breakdowns.
Now you may not have tangled
with the supernatural.
but you've fought monsters.
real freakin' psychos.
Well. you stopped Zeke and Zeb.
Shaggy figured out that
the sharks Old Iron Face rode
were really just torpedoes
disguised to look like sharks.
And what about
the Black Knight? Huh?
Mamba Wamba?
The Space Kook.
I knew it!
You love this show. too.
Mm.
Space Kook.
Ghost Clown.
Miner 49er.
You guys have all
jumped into danger
with no thought for yourselves.
You're heroes. and together.
we're gonna take down
this phantom.
Are you with me?
- Yeah!
- - Let's do it!
But how? We don't know
the first thing about
fighting real ghosts.
We don't have the proper tools
or weapons.
That's okay. We do.
Ooh. Whoa.
Here. Velma. take this.
Sam. are you crazy?
They can't use this stuff.
That's a Scooby-don't.
Dean. we've gotta do something.
I mean.
you guys are amazing!
Thank you. Fred.
But we can help. We have to.
right you can.
You're gonna do what
you do best -- build a trap.
Ahh. That should do it.
Lay it on me. Freddy.
Well. you see.
Daphne's covered all the exits
except that one with salt.
So the phantom will
enter there.
tripping the iron chain
that'll activate the ax.
which cuts the rope
that holds the coconuts.
Where'd he get coconuts?
Shh!
The coconuts are gonna roll.
tripping the phantom.
sending him careening down
a slide of soap.
right into the washing machine
which we'll secure with
those iron chains.
And with the ghost captured.
we can finally find out
what's going on.
Now all we need...is bait.
You think the phantom
decided to leave?
No. it's still here.
Don't worry.
That's what
I'm worried about.
Hmm. Mm-hmm?
Aah! Run!
Aah!
- Shaggy Whoa!
- Aah! Whoa! -
Aah! Whoa!
Ahh. Whoa!
I told you
it wasn't going to work.
Yeah. Fred's traps
never work.
Daph. Plan B!
Operation Bookworm is go.
Aah!
Good shot. Scoob old buddy.
Give him another one.
Scooby. now!
That's a salt circle.
You're stuck.
Let...me...go!
Happy to. Sparky.
soon as you tell us
who you really are.
It's...a child.
Yeah. creepy ghost kid.
You get used to 'em.
But...Wait.
Why are you trying to kill us?
I'm not.
I never wanted to hurt anyone.
But the bad man. he makes me.
The bad man?
His name is Jay.
The dude from the pawnshop.
When I died. my soul was
tied to a pocketknife.
My dad gave it to me.
It meant everything.
When Jay found me.
he used me to...
Sometimes. I get so angry
I break things. hurt people.
But I don't want to.
I just wanna see my dad again.
I'm sorry. It was wrong
of him to do that.
None of this was your fault.
Look. if you get us
back to the real world.
we can set you free.
Do you promise?
Cross my heart
and hope to d--
Well.
you know what I mean.
Should I -- should I make
another trap?
I could get the shotgun!
I could get two shotguns!
Like. tell Scoob and me
when it's over!
Yeah!
Okay. okay. hey.
give me a minute.
We can't leave 'em
like this.
Kid. we need a favor.
- Aah! Uhh!
- Did you send it back
to the fiery pit
from whence it came?!
Look. everything's
under control.
- Aah!
- - Kill it with fire!
Whoa! Slow your roll. guys.
We were wrong.
Huh?
What -- what are you --
what are you saying?
Velma...w-was right.
Like. she was?
This wasn't a real ghost.
We were fooled.
But you never were.
right. Velma?
I. uh...I don't know.
Hey. guys.
do your thing.
This is my favorite part.
Cosgood Creeps?!
But...the flying.
Wires.
Huh.
What about the walking
through the walls?
And the bodies?
Well. that was just
a projector.
As for the bodies...
Were they...dummies filled
with corn syrup?
Huh?
Exactly.
Of course!
Cosgood was trying to drive
everyone from the house
so he could get the money
for himself.
Right. But the joke is on him
because the money's worthless.
It's all
Confederate dollars.
Aw! Oh. well.
Easy come. easy go.
So...
I was right.
I told ya. ya big lug.
There's no such thing as
the supernatural.
Huh?
Looks like you were right.
and now we know.
Hey. my arm's feeling better.
Don't think it was
really broken after all.
This is great news!
Let's meet at the malt shop
and celebrate.
Sure. Fred. And hey.
you're not so bad.
Yeah. I know. Thanks.
So. uh...
I guess this is it.
This is what?
Shh.
No words. We'll never
know what could've been.
Freddy. wait for me!
I will miss your wise words
and your gentle spirits.
Like. we will miss
breathing.
Uhh!Ohh!
Thank you.
You've shown me
the great strength
of laughter in the face
of danger.
Danger?! Where?!
Let's get out of here. man.
- Aah!
- Oh!
Great working with you.
Velma.
You. too. Sam.
Mmm. Mwah.
Those shoulders.
Jinkies!
Shoulda known
Velma was good to go.
Gah! It's always
the quiet ones.
We're ready.
Okay.
That was...something.
That was the coolest thing
that's ever happened to me.
And that includes
the Cartwright twins.
What did you do with
the Cartwright twins?
Oh.
I'll be right back.
I don't think I wanna know.
Well. sorry. sweetheart.
Time to go. kid.
What about the bad man?
Don't worry about him.
We'll take care of him.
all right?
You sure about this?
Look. you're gettin'
this place for a steal.
But...
I'm too old for this crap.
If you say so.
Just. uh.
two more signatures. and...
Not so fast.
Is that an ascot?
Yes.
Yes. it is.
Uh. what are you guys
doing here?
Hey. Alan. your friend here.
he's been driving people
off their property
so he could buy it on the cheap.
And he's been using his own
personal ghost to do it.
You see. he'd plant
the haunted object.
then let the ghost go to work.
Then they would
possess something.
like a big dinosaur
or a perfectly beautiful TV.
And scare people so much that
they'd be desperate to sell.
When we got nosy...
I think we should probably
keep doing some digging.
Everything all right?
Where you gonna put this?
...he sicced
his pet ghost on us.
Take it easy!
What?
She's delicate. all right?
I'll lead. Oh. she...Pfft.
"She"? She? Really. she?
But now. that spirit is freed.
They're lying.
They're...
You think anyone's gonna
believe that?
No. but that's why
we hacked your financials.
Turns out you're not so big
on paying your taxes. are ya?
Good enough for Capone.
good enough for you.
Come on.
Ha! Velma was right.
It was a shady real estate
developer after all.
Here you go.
It's not fair.
I would've gotten away with it
if it wasn't for
those meddling kids.
He said it!
- He said the line!
- Watch your head.
Scooby Dooby Doo!
What are you doing?
Well. I mean. at the end
of every mystery.
Scooby looks into the camera
and he says --
Dean. you're not
a talking dog.
I know that. I...
Yeah.
No. but come on. I-I do
look cool with the ascot. right?
No?
Guys? Come on. guys.
Look. red is my color!
== sync. corrected by elderman ==
@elder_man